<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The Good Code Guy</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The Good Code Guy</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 16:00:28 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nix-Darwin on MacOS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/nixdarwin-on-macos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 15:57:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/nixdarwin-on-macos/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-post&#34;&gt;A post&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I want this post to be a walkthrough of my entire Nix-Darwin setup that allows someone to migrate their world from normal mac to Nix world like that&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blogging with Emacs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/blogging-with-emacs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:33:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/blogging-with-emacs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this post, I&amp;rsquo;m going to show you how to setup a blogging workflow using Emacs and other free tools. At the end of this, you will have a blog just like this one and be able to create posts in a matter of keystrokes that get published online without spending a dime.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t really know how to write these kinds of tutorial posts, so I&amp;rsquo;m just going to get right into it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truth In Tension</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/truth-in-tension/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 21:57:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/truth-in-tension/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We live in a world dominated by the too-quick-to-offend and the offended-too-quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Reality, however, is multi-faceted, each face colored by individual experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our capacity to understand this nuance has lagged behind our access to virtually infinite information.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The result is a breakdown in society, with sects colored by worldviews orchestrated by an unconscious engagement machine, mechanically feeding us whatever data fuels focus and engagement.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the light, this technologically doped filtering is a godsend &amp;ndash; we can find products we love, information we need, people we enjoy, and perspectives we harbor; we become coddled in an instant with whatever cranial comfort we desire.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
