<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Good Code Guy</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Good Code Guy</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:46:18 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You really should use debuggers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/you-really-should-use-debuggers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 10:21:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/you-really-should-use-debuggers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This a post about something near and dear to my heart: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Debuggers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this post, we are going to explain why you should use a debugger, what they are, and how to set them up in your favorite editor d&amp;rsquo;jour (whether that is vscode, neovim, or emacs).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why? Because I believe that quality matters and that by understanding this incredible tool you&amp;rsquo;ll not only have a better time programming, you&amp;rsquo;ll produce better code which is good for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10,000 Monkeys</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/10000-monkeys/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 09:25:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/10000-monkeys/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Artificial intelligence is an incredibly powerful tool that has been building in capability for decades. Only in the last couple of years has it moved into the mainstream and brings with it an incredible set of changes the likes of which we haven&amp;rsquo;t seen since the dawn of the internet.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;10-000-monkeys&#34;&gt;10,000 Monkeys&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s an old adage that goes something like &amp;ldquo;If an infinite number of monkeys typed on an infinite number of typewriters for an infinite time, they would eventually produce the Bible&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My current environment</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-current-environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 18:54:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-current-environment/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll update this post periodically to reflect my current tooling and setup.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;emacs-nix-darwin-macos-and-more&#34;&gt;Emacs, Nix-Darwin, MacOS, and more &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&amp;lt;2025-02-28 Fri&amp;gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now that I&amp;rsquo;ve finished refactoring my entire development and writing environment, why not specify why I&amp;rsquo;m using, what I&amp;rsquo;m using and why? Maybe it&amp;rsquo;ll be useful for you&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;hardware&#34;&gt;Hardware&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;computer--s--macbook-air--apple-silicon--and-x1-carbon--thinkpad&#34;&gt;Computer(s): Macbook Air (Apple Silicon) &amp;amp; X1 Carbon (Thinkpad)&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I use both mac and linux pretty regularly, I have them both configured using &lt;code&gt;Nix&lt;/code&gt; which allows parity between system configurations. New Apple computers are superb, but I can&amp;rsquo;t let go of my Thinkpad because I love tinkering on it and I&amp;rsquo;m sure I&amp;rsquo;ll sell the macbook one day but keep the thinkpad for many more years.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nix-Darwin on MacOS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/nixdarwin-on-macos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 15:57:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/nixdarwin-on-macos/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m going to show you how to setup Nix-Darwin on your Mac to manage your entire computer, its Homebrew packages and more. By the end of this tutorial, you will have your Mac as close to declaratively setup as possible. Let&amp;rsquo;s get started, shall we?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;background&#34;&gt;Background&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-is-nix-darwin&#34;&gt;What is Nix-Darwin?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nix is a declarative (explicitly written) package-manager and system-manager. It can also be a standalone operating system that rivals and perhaps even exceeds Arch in its level of capablity and polish (yes, I have had a fully homebaked version of Arch from scratch and it was awesome).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blogging with Emacs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/blogging-with-emacs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:33:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/blogging-with-emacs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this post, I&amp;rsquo;m going to show you how to setup a blogging workflow using Emacs and other free tools. At the end of this, you will have a blog just like this one and be able to create posts in a matter of keystrokes that get published online without spending a dime.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t really know how to write these kinds of tutorial posts, so I&amp;rsquo;m just going to get right into it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truth In Tension</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/truth-in-tension/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 21:57:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/truth-in-tension/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We live in a world dominated by the too-quick-to-offend and the offended-too-quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Reality, however, is multi-faceted, each face colored by individual experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our capacity to understand this nuance has lagged behind our access to virtually infinite information.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The result is a breakdown in society, with sects colored by worldviews orchestrated by an unconscious engagement machine, mechanically feeding us whatever data fuels focus and engagement.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the light, this technologically doped filtering is a godsend &amp;ndash; we can find products we love, information we need, people we enjoy, and perspectives we harbor; we become coddled in an instant with whatever cranial comfort we desire.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Seth and this is my blog.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-tgcg-dot-xyz&#34;&gt;About tgcg.xyz&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;My primary disclaimer is that the contents here are always evolving and you may encounter opinions that I no longer hold or find advice that is no longer valid.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The purpose of this blog is to give me a space to write about whatever I want. My interests (and hence the content you might encounter) are broad and cover everything from politics &amp;amp; philosophy to computer science &amp;amp; physics.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
